Yasharth Tripathi

Sophomore at VIT. Vellore

Experienced Committee Member with a demonstrated history of working as a front-end developer. Currently learning Back-end development, app development. Strong operations and business development professional with experience in making business and scaling plans for organizations.



- yasharthtripathi@gmail.com
- VELLORE, India
- github.com/yasharthratan

- 8840744576
- in linkedin.com/in/yasharth-tripathi-68612a196
- instagram.com/yasharthratan

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology

Vellore Institute of Technology, Vellore 🗷

07/2019 - Present

Courses

Computer Science

Higher Secondary Education

Sir Padampat Singhania Education Centre

04/2017 - 04/2018

Secondary Education

Methodist High School

04/2015 - 04/2016

WORK EXPERIENCE

Campus Superhero

Coding Blocks 🗷

05/2020 - Present Achievements/Tasks

 I am appointed to carry out operations related to brand awareness and making a presence at events as a Coding

Blocks representative.

 Developing marketing efforts such as posters and social media ads to encourage student participation for campus events.

Campus Ambassador

Alpine Technologies

07/2020 - 08/2020

Achievements/Tasks

 I am appointed to carry out operations related to brand awareness and to carry out the tasks given in the field of digital marketing.

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Leo Club VIT (04/2000 - 07/2000) 🗗

 Official website for the Leo Club VIT, fully responsive giving all the details regarding the club.

Tech Talks 2020 (08/2020 - 09/2020) 🗗

Official website for our Tech Talks graVITas event for the year 2020.

ORGANIZATIONS

CodeChef-VIT (12/2019 - Present) 🖸

Web Developer

SkillShip, Vellore (09/2020 - Present)

Technical Core Member

IEEE-SSIT (09/2020 - Present)

Technical Core Member

CERTIFICATES

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

By Google Digital Garage

Web Designer Basics

By Google

Quicklabs

GCP Cloud Development

LANGUAGES

inglish

Hind

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Cricket

Reading

Movies